export const jsQuizz = {
  questions: [
    {
      question:
        "What course is this?",
      choices: [
        "CSE2103",
        "CSE3140",
        "MATH3160",
        "CSE2102",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "CSE2102",
    },
    {
      question: "How many blue stripes are there on the U.S. flag?",
      choices: [
        "6",
        "7",
        "0",
        "13",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "0",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which number is a multiple of 10",
      choices: ["63", "40", "73", "2"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "40",
    },
    {
      question: "The Agile method is not useful",
      choices: ["True", "False"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "False",
    },
    {
      question: "I stands for Iteration in the SOLD principles ",
      choices: [
        "True",
        "False",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "False",
    },
    {
      question: "What is 4 + 7?",
      choices: [
        "3",
        "2",
        "7",
        "11",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "11",
    },
    {
      question: "Black and pink are the same color",
      choices: [
        "True",
        "False",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "False",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not an IDE",
      choices: [
        "Pycharm",
        "Visual Studio Code",
        "IntelliJ",
        "Skype",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Skype",
    },
    {
      question: "Scrums should happen every 6 months only ",
      choices: [
        "True",
        "False",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "False",
    },
    {
      question: "What is 5 - 3?",
      choices: [
        "4",
        "2",
        "8",
        "10",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "2",
    },
  ],
};

export const resultInitialState = {
score: 0,
correctAnswers: 0,
wrongAnswers: 0

}